- 안녕
-Hey.
밖에 포르셰 세워져 있네
I saw the Porsche parked out front.
열쇠 좀 줘
한 바퀴 돌고 올까 하거든
Can I get the keys?
I'll take that bad boy for a spin.
나한텐 딴 사람 안 빌려
준다더니 로스는 왜 타?
Ross drives it? When I ask, you say
you're the only one allowed to.
오빠잖아, 그리고
운전을 워낙 느리게 하잖아
He's my brother, plus he drives
so slow he couldn't hurt it.
로케트가 아니고
자동차잖아
It's a car, Monica, not a rocket ship.
끝난 다음에
브레이크 등 전구나 갈아 놔
Just replace the bulbs in the
brake lights after you're done.
- 얘들아
- 왔어?
-Hey.
-Hi.
Saw the Porsche. Looking good.
When can I take it out again?
포르셰 봤어, 멋진데
언제 나 또 타도 돼?
- 조이한테도 빌려줬어?
- 난 한 번도 안 탔어
-You let Joey drive it?
-I've never driven it. Not once.
좋아, 한 번 탔다
그래 매일 탄다
Okay, once. Okay, I drive it
all the time.
So much for the "you-can-drive-it
but-don't-tell-Rachel" plan.
레이첼한테 비밀로 하면
운전하게 해준다고 했더니
Wow, I can't believe you lied to me.
나한테 거짓말을 하다니
내가 해결할게, 레이첼은
네가 입만 떼면 결혼식 얘기래
I can fix this. Monica, Rachel thinks
all you talk about is the wedding.
네가 워낙 운전을 함부로 해서
안 빌려주는 거야
I won't let you drive the Porsche
because you're a terrible driver.
There. That wasn't about the wedding.
이건 결혼식 얘기 아니지?
타고 싶으면 내가 몰고
동네 한 바퀴 돌아줄게
If you want a ride in the Porsche,
I'll take you around the block.
두어 시간은 걸리겠다
You got a couple hours?
The One With Chandler's Dad
휴, 정말 끝내줬다
Whew, that was a brisk ride.
- 지붕 내리고 탔구나?
- 그래야 질주할 기분이 나지
-Take the top down, did you?
-Only way to fly.
열쇠 좀 줘
나도 운전 잘 한단 말야
Give me the keys. Monica's wrong.
I'm an excellent driver.
넌 속도광에 무책임해
그러니 운전하면 안 돼
You're fast and irresponsible.
That adds up to a bad driver.
고등학교 땐 그러니까
치어리더가 되던 걸
In high school, that added up
to head cheerleader.
저 여자 나 보는 눈길 봤어?
Did you see how she looked at me?
She must've seen me cruising
in the bad boy.
내가 포르셰 모는 거 봤나 봐
- 네 새둥지 머리 보고 그래
- 뭐라고?
-She's checking out your beehive.
-What?
- 빗 좀 줘
- 열쇠 줘
-Give me a brush.
-The keys.
- 안 돼!
- 그럼 빗도 못 줘
-No way!
-Well, no brush.
Fine. It doesn't matter.
좋아, 필요없어
화장실 바닥에
빗 떨어져 있는 것 봤거든
If I remember correctly, there's
a comb on the floor of the bathroom.
Alimony.
이혼수당이에요
자기 아버지한테서
아직 답신이 안 왔네
We still haven't gotten an
RSVP from your dad.
아마 내가 초대장을
안 보내서 그럴 걸?
Oh, right. Maybe that's because I
didn't send him an invitation.
He's your father.
He should be at our wedding.
자기 아버지야
당연히 오셔야지
우린 가깝지도 않아
못 뵌 지도 몇 년 됐고
I don't even know him.
I haven't seen him in years.
나중에라도 알게 되시면
어쩌려고?
And when he finds out
he wasn't asked?
그럴 리 없어
노는 물이 달라
We don't run in the same circles.
난 너희들하고 놀고
I hang out with you guys and he...
아버진 라스베가스
게이 쇼의 스타셔
stars in a drag show in Vegas.
난 그 물에서 놀고 싶다
I think I want to trade circles.
자기도 아버지 오면 싫을 걸
다들 신부보다는
You don't want him there.
Nobody will stare at the bride...
등 파진 드레스 입은
신랑 아버지 볼 테니까
when the groom's father's
wearing a backless dress.
어때서? 흰 드레스에
베일만 안 쓰면 상관없어
As long as he's not wearing a
white dress and veil, I don't care.
나 옷 좀 사러 가야겠다
I think I need to do some shopping.
죽인다
Nice.
깜짝이야!
My God!
- 지금 뭐 하는 거야?
- 창문 닦고 있어
-What do you think you're doing?
-Just washing the windshield.
너 절대 이 차 운전 못 해
There's no way I'll let you
drive this car.
어서 열쇠 내놔
Just hand over the keys.
Oh!
어머!
Do not start this car.
시동걸지 마
Okay, okay.
I will give you 20 bucks...
좋아, 20달러 줄 테니
당장 이 차에서 내려
if you get out of this car
right now. Hey!
Look.
로스
If you're so freaked out,
get in the car.
그렇게 걱정되면
같이 타면 되잖아
With you? Yeah, right.
너랑? 내가 미쳤어?
All right.
좋아
Okay, okay, okay.
알았어, 알았다고
-What are you doing? Get in front.
-In the death seat?!
- 뭐 해? 앞에 타
- 비명횡사하라구?
-Hey, guys.
-Hi, sweetie.
- 안녕
- 어서 와, 자기
-Ready to go?
-My purse is at Mon's. I'll be back.
- 갈까?
- 모니카네서 핸드백 가져 올게
-Wait a minute.
-What? Oh.
- 잠깐만
- 뭔데? 아
That one kept going.
효과 오래 가는데
So, you and Phoebe, huh?
피비하고 사귄다구요?
-How long have you been going out?
-A month.
- 얼마나 된 거죠?
- 한 달 넘었어요
그럼 우리 인사나 하고 지내요
We ought to get to
know each other better.
-Sure. I'd like that.
-Yeah. So, uh...
- 그래요, 좋아요
- 네, 그럼...
What's your name?
이름이 뭐예요?
-It's Jake.
-Joey.
- 제이크
- 조이
-Do you like the Knicks?
-Yeah, big fan.
- 닉스 좋아해요?
- 그럼요, 광팬이죠
Me too. There's a game Tuesday.
Do you want to go?
나도요, 화요일에
시합 있는데 같이 갈래요?
Great! Let me make sure I'm not
doing anything Tuesday.
좋아요! 그 날 별일 없나
확인해 보고요
Here.
여기
-What's this?
-Your suitcase. We're going to Vegas.
- 그게 뭐야?
- 라스베가스에 가는 거야
Are you serious? Eloping?
No more stupid wedding stuff.
정말? 비밀리에 결혼하자고?
거창한 결혼식 말고?
이 꽃, 저 꽃 안 고르고
그럼 돈 무지 절약되겠다
No more these flowers, these flowers.
Think of the money we'll save.
We're not eloping.
Can our wedding be bigger, please?
아니구나? 나 꽃 좋아해
결혼식 더 크게 할까?
We're going to see your dad.
아버님 만나러 가는 거야
나도 시아버님
뵙고 싶다고
I want to get to know
my father-in-law.
When we went over this, I won.
이미 이 얘기 끝났고
내가 이겼잖아
No, you didn't.
Honey, just so you know...
안 이겼어
자기, 그리고 말야
Now that you're marrying me,
you don't get to win anymore.
나랑 결혼하면 앞으로
절대 이길 일 없을 거야
Forget it. I don't want to go.
I don't want to see him.
싫어, 난 안 가
아버지 만나기 싫어
I know your dad embarrassed you.
아버지 때문에
창피했었다는 거 알아
아이들은 다
부모님이 창피하지
All kids are embarrassed
by their parents.
그렇지만 난
차원이 달랐다구
You need a new word
for what I went through.
In high school,
he came to all my swim meets...
고교시절엔
내 수영대회 때마다
매번 다른 여배우 복장으로
나타나셨어
dressed as a Hollywood starlet.
안 그래도 힘든 사춘긴데
Hard enough to be 14, skinny, wearing
Speedos Mom promised I'd grow into.
깡마르고 엄마가 골라 준
터무니없이 큰 수영복에
You look up in the stands.
There's your dad cheering you on.
스탠드를 보면 아버지가
응원하고 계셨지
카멘 미란다처럼 차려입고
진짜 과일이 달린
Dressed as Carmen Miranda, wearing
a headdress with real fruit...
모잘 쓰셨지, 나중에
과일은 애들에게 나눠 주시고
that he'll later give to your
friends as a healthy snack.
He was at every one of your swim meets
cheering you on.
중요한 건 수영대회 때마다
응원 오셨단 거야
That's a pretty great dad.
그럼 훌륭한 아빠 아냐?
He had sex with Mr. Garibaldi.
아버진 개리볼디씨랑 잤어
-Who's Mr. Garibaldi?
-Does it matter?!
- 개리볼디씨가 누구야?
- 그게 지금 중요해?
You're not 14 anymore, okay? Maybe
it's time you let that stuff go.
자긴 14살이 아니야
이젠 용서할 때도 됐어
If he's not at your wedding, you'll
regret it for the rest of your life.
아버님이 결혼식 안 오시면
자기 평생 후회할 거야
Okay, but I'm just doing this for you.
좋아, 자기 때문에 가는 거다
-I never get to win anymore?
-How much did you ever win before?
- 나 이젠 절대 못 이긴다고?
- 언제는 이겼어?
You know how when you're wearing
pants and you lean forward...
너 바지 입었을 때
앞으로 숙이면
내가 네 속옷 보는 거 알지?
I check out your underwear?
Well, when Jake did it...
제이크가 숙였을 때
I saw that he was wearing
women's underwear.
보니까 여자 속옷
입고 있더라
알아, 내 거야
I know. They were mine.
Oh!
아!
No, no, wait. That's weird.
잠깐, 그래도 이상해
We were goofing around,
and I dared him to try them on.
서로 장난치다가
내가 입어보라고 했어
That's weird!
그래도 이상해!
-I'm wearing his briefs right now.
-That's kind of hot.
- 난 제이크 속옷 입었어
- 그건 섹시하다
I think so too. And that little flap?
Great for holding my lipstick.
그렇지? 앞에 그 부분
립스틱 넣기 딱 좋더라
I wouldn't know about that.
그 생각은 못 해봤네
Jake says that women's underwear
is actually more comfortable.
제이크 말이
여자 속옷이 더 편하대
He loves how silk feels
against his skin.
실크 감촉이 너무 좋다나
Next he'll say your high heels
are good for his posture.
다음엔 하이힐이
자세에 좋다고 하겠다
There's nothing wrong with Jake.
He is all man.
제이크한텐 문제없어
얼마나 남자다운데
I think more than you.
너보다 남자다울 걸
He looked like a real lumberjack
in those pink lacies.
그래 핑크 속옷 입으니
진짜 남자답더라
Only a man completely secure
in his masculinity could...
자신의 남성다움에
자신있는 남자만이
walk around in women's underwear.
I don't think you could.
여자 속옷을 입을 수
있다는 거야, 넌 못 할 걸
-I am secure with my masculinity.
-Okay, whatever.
- 난 남성다움에 자신 있어
- 그렇다고 치자
내 방에 포르노 잡지
쌓인 거 봤지?
You've seen my huge stack of porn.
운전하니 너무 좋다
God, I forgot how much I love driving.
I have got to get my license renewed.
면허증 갱신해야지
너 그럼 면허증도 없이?
당장 차 세워
You don't have a valid driver's
license? Pull over right now.
로스, 왜 그래?
그냥 긴장 풀어
You're so tense.
You just gotta relax, okay?
Okay? Just need to relax. All right?
Just need to relax.
긴장을 풀고
편안히 즐겨
뭐 해? 재미없어
장난치지 마
What are you..? That's not funny.
Stop horsing around.
장난치는 게 아냐
I am not horsing around, okay?
포르셰 모는 거지
I am "Porsche-ing" around.
Uh-oh.
어머나
진정해, 아무 일 없을 거야
별로 잘못한 것 없어
Stay calm. Nothing will happen.
You're not in that much trouble.
Really? You think so?
정말? 그럴까?
I'm talking to myself.
You're going down!
내 얘기한 거야
넌 이제 끝장이야!
'포 퀸즈'
Has someone taken your order?
주문하셨어요?
네, 저 여자분, 아니
저 남자분, 여잔가?
Oh, yeah. She did. He did. She?
I'm sorry, I'm new. I don't...
미안해요, 처음이라...
- 맥주 시켰어요
- 게이 아니라고요, 알아요
-I just ordered a beer.
-You're straight. I get it.
아버님한테 전화했으면
좋은 자리 주셨을 텐데
If we called your dad,
we'd have better seats.
아직 우리 온 거
알리고 싶지 않아
I don't want him to know we're
here yet. I'm not ready.
게다가 아버지도 별로
날 보고 싶지 않을 거야
He won't be too happy
to see me either.
왜?
Why not?
말했는지 모르겠는데
He's kind of tried to contact me...
몇 년 동안 나한테
연락하려고 애쓰셨거든
-a lot the last few years.
-What?
뭐라고?
Yeah. He's made phone calls,
written letters.
전화도 하고
편지도 보내시고
찾아도 오셨는데
매번 바쁘다고 했어
He came to New York.
I said I was too busy.
It's very "Cats in the Cradle."
I don't want to get into it.
좀 복잡한 얘기야
이 정도만 할래
Here we go.
시작한다
신사, 숙녀 여러분
소개합니다
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome the incomparable...
헬레나 핸드배스킷
Helena Handbasket.
안녕하세요
Hello, darlings.
우리 아빠야
And there's Daddy.
자리 바꾸자, 어서
내가 밑으로 네가 위로 와
Switch places with me. Come on!
I'll go under, you go over.
- 그래, 좋은 생각이다
- 어서!
-Yeah, I'll get right on that.
-Come on!
What? No. Hey, Rach, come on.
- 뭐 해? 레이첼, 하지마
- 얼른!
I'm sure we won't get arrested
for this.
이런 건 체포감 안 되겠다
젠장!
Hi, officer.
Was I going a little too fast?
안녕하세요, 경관님
제가 너무 빨리 갔나요?
가관이다
Oh, my God.
-Can I see your license, please?
-Absolutely.
- 면허증 좀 보여주시죠?
- 그럼요
It's weird. I had a dream last night
that I was stopped by a policeman.
이상하네요, 어제 경관이
차 세우는 꿈 꿨거든요
그런데, 그분이...
And then he...
Well, I probably shouldn't
tell you the rest.
그 다음 얘긴
안 하는 게 좋겠네요
- 면허증요?
- 네, 여기요
-Your license.
-Yes. Here you go, Officer...
Handsome.
핸섬 씨
- 핸슨입니다
- 이런, 죄송해요
-It's Hanson.
-Oops, sorry. My mistake.
못 봐주겠네!
Dear Lord!
- 와!
- 너 죽었다
-Wow!
-Here it comes.
This is a great picture.
사진 잘 나왔네요
그래요? 금방
자다 깨서 찍은 건데
Really? You think so? You know,
I had just rolled right out of bed.
아주 멋지네요!
You look phenomenal.
당연하죠!
10년 전에 찍은 건데!
She should!
It was taken 10 years ago!
날짜가 좀 이상하다
생각하시겠죠?
You know, you probably...
wonder about the old date.
네, 물병자리군요
Yes. You're an Aquarius, huh?
- 경관님은 쌍둥이자리
- 아뇨
-I'll bet you're a Gemini.
-No.
- 황소자리?
- 아뇨
-Taurus?
-No.
-Virgo?
- 처녀자리?
- 아뇨
-Sagittarius?
-Yep.
- 궁수자리?
- 맞아요
I knew it. I knew it!
그럴 줄 알았어요
- 이젠 속도 위반하지 말아요
- 안 할게요
You won't speed anymore, right?
I won't speed.
- 면허증도 갱신하시고요
- 물론이죠
-Promise to take care of this?
-I promise.
친구분께 운전하라고 해요
면허증은 있죠?
Let him drive.
Does he have a license?
- 수동도 몰 수 있나요?
- 글쎄요...
-Can he handle a stick?
-Well...
수동도 몰 수 있어요!
I can handle a stick!
-That can't be your father.
-I've been saying that for years.
- 저 사람이 자기 아버지일 리가?
- 내가 평생 하던 말이야
- 맙소사!
- 왜?
-Oh, my God!
-What?
피아노치는 사람
개리볼디씨야
That's Mr. Garibaldi
playing the piano.
안녕하세요, 환영합니다
Hello, and welcome to the show.
손님 중에 단골도 있고
I see some of our regulars
in the audience.
단골이 아닌 분도
더러 있네요
And a couple of irregulars.
- 관중석으로 오셔
- 걱정 마, 괜찮을 거야
-He's coming into the audience.
-Relax. You'll be fine.
훨 낫다, 이제
자기 안 보이네
Oh, much better.
You're invisible now.
- 어디서 왔죠?
- 베이커스필드요
-Where are you from?
-Bakersfield.
- 뭐라고요?
- 베이커스필드요
-I'm sorry?
-Bakersfield.
알아요, 안 됐네요
No, no, I heard. I'm just sorry.
이렇게 만나긴 싫어
호텔에서 봐
I'll meet you back at the hotel.
벌써 가시려고요?
금방 시작했는데
Look, a standing ovation already.
So early in the show.
돌아서요, 자기
예쁜 얼굴 좀 보게
Turn around, darling.
Let me see your pretty face.
여기 술 좀 가져와요
웨이터? 웨이트리스?
Can we have our drinks, please?
Waiter? tress?
-Hey, Phoebe.
-Hey.
- 안녕, 피비
- 왔어?
Check it out.
이거 봐라
나 정말 남자답지?
How much of a man am I?
와, 멋지다
남자답고 조금 헤프게도 보여
Wow, nice.
Manly, and also kind of a slut.
제이크의 말이
이해가 갈 것 같아
I'm beginning to see what Jake
was talking about.
The silk feels really good.
실크 감촉 정말 좋다
And things aren't as smashed down
as I thought they would be.
생각만큼
꽉 끼지도 않고 말야
잘 됐네
That's great.
남자 속옷보다
선택의 폭도 넓잖아
You have so many more choices
than with men's underwear.
비키니, 끈 달린 거
옷감도 면, 실크, 레이스
Bikini, French cut, thong.
And the fabrics: cotton, silk, lace.
항상 궁금한 게 있었어
팬티 스타킹
You know what I've always
wondered about? Pantyhose!
발가락에서 시작해서
여기 끝까지 주욱...
The way they start at your toe,
then they go all the way up to..
-I should go take these off.
-I think it's important you do.
- 나 이거 벗어야겠지?
- 그래, 얼른 벗어
What's your name?
이름이 뭐죠?
Chandler.
챈들러요
챈들러?
Chandler?
What an unusual name.
이름이 특이하네요
You must have had terribly
fascinating parents.
부모님이 아주 재미있는
분들이셨나 봐요
Oh, they're a hoot.
그럼요
친구분은?
And who is your friend?
모니카예요
I'm Monica.
- 모니카, 어디서 왔죠?
- 뉴욕에서요
-Monica. Where are you from?
-New York.
I'm not very fond of New York.
Queens, I like.
난 뉴욕은 별론데
퀸즈는 좋아하죠
이건 뭐죠?
What is this...
번쩍이는 거 말예요
sparkling something, honey, huh?
모니카와 전 약혼했어요
Actually, Monica and I are engaged.
Really?
그래요?
축하해요
Congratulations.
결혼식은 언제죠?
When's the big day?
In two weeks.
2주 후에 해요
그렇군요
I see.
Well, I wish you both
a lifetime of happiness.
두 사람 평생
행복하시길 바래요
So, you're bald.
댁은 대머리군요
잠깐만요
Wait, wait.
We'd love it if you could be there.
결혼식에 와 주셨음 해요
정말요?
Really?
그래 주시면 기쁠 거예요
I know it would make me happy...
ma'am.
부인
Then I wouldn't miss it for the world.
그럼 무슨 일이 있어도 가야죠
왜 눈앞이 흐려지지
I'm getting all misty here.
You'd think I was having my legs waxed
or something.
다리 털을 뽑고 있는 것도
아닌데 말야
- 괜찮아?
- 응
-You okay?
-Yeah.
Thanks for making me do this.
데려와줘서 고마워
쇼 시작하기 전에
신랑 신부에게
Before we go on with the show, I want
to say to the bride and groom...
서로를 찾아서 잘 됐다고
말해주고 싶네요
how lucky they are to have
found each other.
살다보면 비도 내리는 법
In every life a little rain must fall.
다행히도
Fortunately...
in my life...
내 인생엔...
When I was growing up, I played
the one on the far left.
나 어렸을 때
맨 왼쪽 남자 역했어
너한테 소개시켜 줄
사람 있어
Remind me to introduce you
to someone.
- 누구?
- 4단 기어
-Who?
-Fourth gear.
왜 그러지?
난 잘못한 거 없는데
What does he want?
I wasn't doing anything.
손이 10시와 2시 방향에서
벗어났나 보지
Maybe he saw your hands slip briefly
from the 10 and 2:00 position.
Maybe it's Sergeant Sagittarius
coming back to flirt some more.
아마 궁수자리께서
시시덕거리고 싶은 가보지
It's a different guy.
다른 사람이야
-Good evening, sir.
-Do you know how fast you were going?
- 안녕하세요, 경관님
- 속도가 얼마였는지 아세요?
아뇨, 하지만 95킬로
이하였을 텐데요
No, I don't, but it couldn't
have been more than 60.
맞아요, 60이었죠
You're right. It was 37.
너무 천천히 갔다고
딱지를 떼겠단 겁니까?
You're not ticketing me
for driving too slow, are you?
That's right.
맞습니다
저, 경관님
You know, officer...
I had the weirdest dream last night.
어제 이상한 꿈을 꿨답니다
Oh, my God!
못 봐주겠군!
면허증 주시죠
Your license, please.
You don't want to hear
about my dream...
꿈 얘기
궁금하지 않으세요
Officer...
프리티
Pretty?
경관님?
It's Petty.
페티입니다
I'll be right back with your ticket.
딱지갖고 오겠습니다
-You have a son.
-I know. I know.
- 넌 아들도 있어
- 나도 알아
-Feel better?
-Yeah. Much.
- 기분 좀 나아졌어?
- 그래, 훨씬
있잖아
Listen...
Not that I'm insecure about
my manhood or anything, but...
내 남성다움에 자신이
없다는 건 아니지만
당장 여자 하나
꼬셔야겠다
I need to hook up with
a woman right now.
그래
I understand.
You look familiar. Do I know you?
낯이 익은데, 저 아세요?
I don't think so.
아뇨
Maybe it's because I'm on television.
내가 TV에 나와서 그런가 봐요
-I'm an actor on Days of our Lives.
-Wow. Really?
- 생의 나날들에 출연하거든요
- 와, 그래요?
-$4.50, please.
-Oh, let me get this.
- 4달러 50센트요
- 제가 내죠
These are for you.
이건 당신 주려고요